codecollege.ca 2018-09-03

# Code College Privacy Policy | Code College

## Privacy Policy

Brightside Studios Inc. Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from CodeCollege.ca (the “School”). 

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

When you visit the School, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the School, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the School, and information about how you interact with the School. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.” 

We collect Device Information using the following technologies: 

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. 

\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the School, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. 

\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the School. 

We use a Third-Party Service called Teachable.com to process orders on the School. Through Teachable.com, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, or phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” 

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information. 

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? 

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the School (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: 

Communicate with you; 

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and 

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. 

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the School, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). 

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Teachable.com to power our online store--you can read more about how Teachable uses your Personal Information here: <https://teachable.com/privacy-policy>. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the School--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. 

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING 

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work. 

You can opt out of targeted advertising by: 

FACEBOOK - <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>

GOOGLE - <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>

BING - [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/reso...](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/. 

DO NOT TRACK 

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser. 

YOUR RIGHTS 

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. 

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the School), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States. 

DATA RETENTION 

When you place an order through the School, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. 

CHANGES 

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. 

CONTACT US 

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at brad@brightsidestudios.ca.
